The Peter Bekker Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Peter Bekker, Jr.
  - Subseries 1.8 Audio Recordings, Cassettes are organized alphabetically
    - Subseries 1.8.1 Cassettes
      - [Altan] Lorena McKennit Altan \The Mask/Mirror- The Mystic Dream/The Bonny Swans/The Dark Night and Dark Souls/Marrakesh Night Marbos/Full Circle/Santiago/ The 2 Trees \Prospero's Speech- Tommy Peoples The Windmill/Beidg Oyn, Artist: Altan Length: 01.43.07 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.3.mp3, 1.8.1.11.3.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 3)
      - [Anderson, Laurie] Translator Laurie Anderson Tommy Tutone, Artist: Laurie Anderson Length: 01:335:42 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.4.mp3, 1.8.1.11.4.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 4)
      - [Anderson, Laurie] Shakuhachi / Laurie Anderson, Artist: Laurie Anderson Length: 01:03:57 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.5.mp3, 1.8.1.11.5.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 5)
      - [Anka, Paul] Interview Paul Anka #1, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:58 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.6.mp3, 1.8.1.11.6.wav (Box 11, Cassette 6)
      - [Anka, Paul] Interview Paul Anka #2, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:59 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.7.mp3, 1.8.1.11.7.wav (Box 11, Cassette 7)
      - [Anka, Paul] Interview Paul Anka #3, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:58 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.8.mp3, 1.8.1.11.8.wav (Box 11, Cassette 8)
      - [Anka, Paul] Between the Lines: Paul Anka 1-10, 11-20, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:14 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.9.mp3, 1.8.1.11.9.wav (Box 11, Cassette 9)
      - [Armstrading, Joan] Joan Armstrading 26 Apr 55 ATM/NYC, Artist: Joan Armstrading Length: 00:18:26 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.10.mp3, 1.8.1.11.10.wav (Box 11, Cassette 10)
      - [Athens, Art] WCBS Special Report: Son of Sam 44-Caliber killer. 8-11-77. Anchored by Art Athens, Artist: Art Athens Length: 00:27:37 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.11.mp3, 1.8.1.11.11.wav (Box 11, Cassette 11)
      - [Athens, Art] Elvis Presley: a retrospective Art Athens, WCBS Radio 8-16-77, Artist: Art Athens Length: 00:06:27 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.12.mp3, 1.8.1.11.12.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 12)
      - [Bagger, Justice] Comedy- Justice Bagger, Artist: Justice Bagger Length: 00:02:52 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.13.mp3, 1.8.1.11.13.wav (Box 11, Cassette 13)
      - [Barron, Richard] 80's MB Music -Randazzo Richard Barron., Artist: Richard Barron Length: 00:10:40 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.14.mp3, 1.8.1.11.14.wav (Box 11, Cassette 14)
      - [Barron, Richard] Richard Barron- Nrml eq, no dolby- + heartbreaker + take a ride + feeling like I do w/vocals (weak), Artist: Richard Barron Length: 00:11:32 Type: Demo File Names: 1.8.1.11.15.mp3, 1.8.1.11.15.wav (Box 11, Cassette 15)
      - [Barron, Richard] Richard Baron trax (3) Soundworks NYC \ Richie Baron no vocal, Artist: Richard Barron Length: 00:27:44 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.16.mp3, 1.8.1.11.16.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 16)
      - [The Beatles] Bruce Springsteen - Born in the USA Sgt. Pepper, Artist: The Beatles Length: 01:34:45 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.17.mp3, 1.8.1.11.17.wav (Box 11, Cassette 17)
      - [The Beatles] Beatles Interview 6, Artist: George Harrison Length: 01:32:42 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.18.mp3, 1.8.1.11.18.wav (Box 11, Cassette 18)
      - [The Beatles] The Beatles One, Artist: The Beatles Length: 01:40:40 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.19.mp3, 1.8.1.11.19.wav (Box 11, Cassette 19)
      - [The Beatles] The Beatles 2, Artist: The Beatles Length: 01:02:03 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.20.mp3, 1.8.1.11.20.wav (Box 11, Cassette 20)
      - [The Beatles] Beatles Montage, Artist: The Beatles Length: 00:07:19 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.21.mp3, 1.8.1.11.21.wav (Box 11, Cassette 21)
      - [Bekker, Peter] Grammy Awards- Radio City 2/25/81, 25-Feb-81; Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:50:13 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.22.mp3, 1.8.1.11.22.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 22)
      - [Bekker, Peter] CBS Radio Network 2x "Grammy Awards Preview" Peter Bekker, Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:50:13 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.23.mp3, 1.8.1.11.23.wav (Box 11, Cassette 23)
      - [Bekker, Peter] Microbase, Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:39:300 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.24.mp3, 1.8.1.11.24.wav (Box 11, Cassette 24)
      - [Bekker, Peter] MicroBase/Wendy Callins, Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:59:54 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.25.mp3, 1.8.1.11.25.wav (Box 11, Cassette 25)
      - [Bekker, Peter] In The MicroBase- 21 segments, Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:37:17 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.26.mp3, 1.8.1.11.26.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 26)
      - [Bellamy, David] Patrick Simmons - 4/7/1983 Elektra - la David Bellamy merv griffin theatre Andy Pierce Epic records 4/8 Carl Wilson rogers & cowan 4/12, Artist: La David Bellamy Length: 01:30:39 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.27.mp3, 1.8.1.11.27.wav See folder for 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 27)
      - [Bernstein, Peter] Peter Bernstein/Mark Goldenberg Cretones 3/2/81 EA/KA Mark Case- Plimsouls ditto Mark Saffan 3/2/81 EA/LA, 1981; Artist: Peter Bernstein Length: 00:01:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.28.mp3, 1.8.1.11.28.wav (Box 11, Cassette 28)
      - [Between the Lines: Paul Anka] Interview Paul Anka #1, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:58 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.6.mp3, 1.8.1.11.6.wav (Box 11, Cassette 6)
      - [Between the Lines: Paul Anka] Interview Paul Anka #2, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:59 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.7.mp3, 1.8.1.11.7.wav (Box 11, Cassette 7)
      - [Between the Lines: Paul Anka] Interview Paul Anka #3, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 00:16:51 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.8.mp3, 1.8.1.11.8.wav (Box 11, Cassette 8)
      - [Between the Lines: Paul Anka] Between the Lines: Paul Anka 1-10, 11-20, Artist: Paul Anka Length: 01:02:14 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.9.mp3, 1.8.1.11.9.wav (Box 11, Cassette 9)
      - [Between the Lines: Barry Manilow] WJOY-BVT: Between/Lines Manilow. Syracuse U. Prof. Marvin Druger with 2 Australian air traffic controllers, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 00:52:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.29.mp3, 1.8.1.11.29.wav (Box 11, Cassette 29)
      - [Between the Lines: Barry Manilow] Between the Lines: Barry Manilow 1-10, 11-20, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 01:35:37 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.30.mp3, 1.8.1.11.30.wav (Box 11, Cassette 30)
      - [Between the Lines: Barry Manilow] Interview Barry Manilow #1 Manilow 1 Manilow 2, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 01:05;55 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.31.mp3, 1.8.1.11.31.wav (Box 11, Cassette 31)
      - [Between the Lines: Barry Manilow] Interview Barry Manilow #3 Manilow 3 Manilow 4, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 00:45:07 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.32.mp3, 1.8.1.11.32.wav (Box 11, Cassette 32)
      - [Between the Lines:Hall and Oates] Between the Lines: Hall & Oates #1-10, #11-20, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:02:00 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.33.mp3, 1.8.1.11.33.wav (Box 11, Cassette 33)
      - [Between the Lines:Hall and Oates] Between the Lines: Hall & Oates segments 1-10 CBS Radio Peter Bekker \Between the Lines: Hall & Oates segments 11-20 peter bekker, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:22:29 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.34.mp3, 1.8.1.11.34.wav (Box 11, Cassette 34)
      - [Between the Lines:Hall and Oates] Daryl Hall/John Oates-Genya Ravan Balde Silva - Muse News conference\ 1) balde silva wcbs 9/18/79 * MUSE harvey wasserman, james taylor, john hall, graham nash, bonnie raitt * stsler hilton 9/19/79\2) Daryll Hall /John Oates 45 Sheridan sq, nyc 9/25/79 Genya Ravan cbs 10/17/79, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:02:04 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.35.mp3, 1.8.1.11.35.wav (Box 11, Cassette 35)
        Cannot find casset, pretty sure different recordings
      - [Blotto] Gene Simmons /Nona Hendry x Blotto /Alabama, Artist: Blotto Length: 01:24:43 Type: Interview File Names: 1.7.1.11.2.mp3, 1.7.1.11.2.wav (Box 11, Cassette 2)
      - [Browne, Jackson] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: Jackson Browne Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Bush, Kate] Kate Bush "The Dreaming" and… "Mexican Radio & Walking Voodoo" Randy Newman "Trouble in Paradise"/"Hungry Wolf", Artist: Kate Bush Length: 01:32:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.37.mp3, 1.8.1.11.37.wav (Box 11, Cassette 37)
      - [Bush, Kate] Kate Bush Lion Heart Wuthering Heights, Artist: Kate Bush Length: 01:28:47 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.38.mp3, 1.8.1.11.38.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 38)
      - [Bush, Kate] Kate Bush, Artist: Kate Bush Length: 01:31:52 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.39.mp3, 1.8.1.11.39.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 39)
      - [The Cars] The Cars - Candy O., Artist: The Cars Length: 01:18:45 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.40.mp3, 1.8.1.11.40.wav (Box 11, Cassette 40)
      - [The Cars] Shake it up/ heartbeat city, Artist: The Cars Length: 01:27:46 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.41.mp3, 1.8.1.11.41.wav (Box 11, Cassette 41)
      - [The Cars] The Cars - Panorama, Artist: The Cars Note: Cassette does not play (Box 11, Cassette 42)
      - [The Cars] The Cars - Panorama Ric O - Beatitutde, Artist: The Cars Length: 01:33:58 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.1.mp3, 1.8.1.12.1.wav (Box 12, Cassette 1)
      - [CBS] A Remembering 1939/6 pieces/may 1989/mike walker 50th- war of the worlds oct '88 (5 pieces) "CBS at 60"9/8 Remembering World War 2-20 pieces April 1983- 60 minutes- 20 going on 21- 5 pieces 1988, Artist: CBS Length: 01:14:48 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.2.mp3, 1.8.1.12.2.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 2)
      - [CBS] John Lennon * CBS Radio 12/9/80 \John Lennon Murder * vigil 12/14/80 - wnew-fm & cbs radio osgood retrospective -pboy ivue, Artist: CBS Length: 00:58:21 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.3.mp3, 1.8.1.12.3.wav (Box 12, Cassette 3)
      - [CBS] News Mark CBS news "D-Day", Artist: CBS Length: 00:30:10 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.4.mp3, 1.8.1.12.4.wav (Box 12, Cassette 4)
      - [Chanier, Clifton] Clifton Chanier Queen Ida, Artist: Clifton Chanier Length: 01:07:28 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.5.mp3, 1.8.1.12.5.wav (Box 12, Cassette 5)
      - [The Chieftans] Ladysmith- Shaka Zulu Morrison/Chieftans- Irish Heart \ B: Morrison-Chieftans Star of The County Down/Irish Heartbeat/ TAMO Chleamhnas Deanta/ Raglanroaa/ She Moved The Fair/ I'll Tell Me Ma/ Carrickfergus/ Celtic Ray/ My Lagan Love/ Maries Wedding \ A: Ladysmith- Unomathemba/ Hello My Baby/ At Golgotha/ King of Kings/ The Earth Is Never Satisfied/ How Long?/ Home of the Heroes/ These Are The Guys/ Rain, Rain Beautiful Rain? Who Were U Talking To?, Artist: The Chieftans Length: 01:27:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.6.mp3, 1.8.1.12.6.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 6)
      - [Chittlun, Blind Lemon] An Evening with Blind Lemon Chittlun For Headphones only, Artist: Blind Lemon Chittlun Length: 00:51:21 Type: Music/Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.7.mp3, 1.8.1.12.7.wav (Box 12, Cassette 7)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Mitchell Clarvit- Basic trax (3) 5/7/81 unique recorders, nyc., Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:41:37 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.8.mp3, 1.8.1.12.8.wav (Box 12, Cassette 8)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Mitchell Clarvit Rock Mitchell Kamikaze Lover, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:19:11 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.9.mp3, 1.8.1.12.9.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 9)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Mitchell Clarvit Like a song - Coward - Do you really love this guy - out the door - Kamikaza Lover, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:16:53 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.10.mp3, 1.8.1.12.10.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 10)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Mitchell Clarvit Like a song - coward - sacrifice- Mexico under control L.A. Sun San Diego, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:24:03 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.11.mp3, 1.8.1.12.11.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 11)
      - [Clarvit, Mitch] Mitch Clarvit Squeeze it (to the last drop) Love's gunna take you Kamikaze lover It takes two Out the door All songs © 1981-83 M. Clarvit & D. Perman, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:18:51 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.12.mp3, 1.8.1.12.12.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 12)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Mitch Clarvit Out The Door\ It Takes Two, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:08:10 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.13.mp3, 1.8.1.12.13.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 13)
      - [Clarvit, Mitchell] Outtakes Mitchell Clarvit Sacrifice- Out the door- Kamikaze lover Acoustic Mitchell Clarvit (3) demo, Artist: Mitchell Clarvit Length: 00:08:45 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.14.mp3, 1.8.1.11.24.wav (Box 12, Cassette 14)
      - [Collins, Paul] TOM SCOTT- PAUL COLLINS/BOB GELDOFF- SHEEN MEMORIAL 5 TOM SCOTT/berkshire pl hotel #1521 12/7/79 * MEMORIAL FOR FULTON SHEET/st. pat's 12/10 cooke + McGarrick PAUL COLLINS/(the beat) WCBS 12/12 BOB GELDORF (boomtown rats) berkshire pl hotel #908 12/14/79 5, Artist: Paul Collins Length: 01:38:12 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.15.mp3, 1.8.1.12.15.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 15)
      - [Collins, Wendy] Microbase, Artist: Wendy Collins Length: 00:39:300 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.24.mp3, 1.8.1.11.24.wav (Box 11, Casette 24)
      - [Cooder, Ry] Ry Cooder - Got Rhythmn Rubble Robantson, Artist: Ry Cooder Length: 01:29:23 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.16.mp3, 1.8.1.12.16.wav (Box 12, Cassette 16)
      - [Crenshaw, Marshall] Someday/Someway Various \ Men @ work various, Artist: Marshall Crenshaw Length: 01:03:11 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.17.mp3, 1.8.12.17.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 17)
      - [Cretones] Peter Bernstein/Mark Goldenberg Cretones 3/2/81 EA/KA Mark Case- Plimsouls ditto Mark Saffan 3/2/81 EA/LA, 1981; Artist: Cretones Length: 00:01:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.28.mp3, 1.8.1.11.28.wav (Box 11, Cassette 28)
      - [DC 5] DC 5/Ventures/Brenda Lee, Artist: DC 5 Length: 00:46:16 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.18.mp3, 1.8.1.12.18.wav (Box 12, Cassette 18)
      - [Denny, Sandy] Sandy Denny 1+2, Artist: Sandy Denny Length: 01:28:59 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.19.mp3, 1.8.1.12.19.wav (Box 12, Cassette 19)
      - [Denny, Sandy] Sandy Denny 3+4, Artist: Sandy Denny Length: 01:37:38 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.20.mp3, 1.8.1.12.20.wav (Box 12, Cassette 20)
      - [Derek and the Dominos] Derek and Dominos, Artist: Derek and the Dominos Length: 00:40:23 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.12.21.mp3, 1.8.12.21.wav (Box 12, Cassette 21)
      - [DeVille, Mink] Mink DeVille (2) \ Cabretta- Venus Ave D/Little Girl/ 1 Way Street/ Mixed Up Girl/Gunslinger/Can It Do Without It/Cadillac Walk/Spanish Stroll/Party Girls \Where Angels Fear To Tread- Each Word/River of Tears/Demasiado Corazun/Lilly's Daddys Caddy/Around The Corner/Pick Up The Pieces/Loves Got a Hold On Me/Keep Your Monkey/Moonlight Let Me Down, Artist: Mink DeVille Length: Music Type: 01:16:33 File Names: 1.8.1.12.22.mp3, 1.8.1.12.22.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 22)
      - [DeVille, Mink] Mink DeVille (2) \ Le Chat Bleu- This must be the night/savior faire/that world outside/slow drain/U just keep holdin on/lipstick traces/walk that girl home/every way but loose/bad boy/Heavens too still \Coup De Grace- 1 good reason/help me to make it/maybe tomorrow/teardrops must fall/you better moce on/love + emotion/So in love/like you did before/made in heaven/end of the line, Artist: Mink DeVille Length: 01:26:43 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.23.mp3, 1.8.1.12.23.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 23)
      - [Dire Straits] Dire Straits/Live, Artist: Dire Straits Length: 01:33:00 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.24.mp3, 1.8.1.12.24.wav (Box 12, Cassette 24)
      - [Dire Straits] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: Dire Straits Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Divan] Talking Heads - Sense Divan, Artist: Divan Length: 01:32:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.25.mp3, 1.8.1.12.25.wav (Box 12, Cassette 25)
      - [Druger, Marvin] WJOY-BVT: Between/Lines Manilow. Syracuse U. Prof. Marvin Druger with 2 Australian air traffic controllers, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 00:52:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.29.mp3, 1.8.1.11.29.wav (Box 11, Cassette 29)
      - [Elektra] Patrick Simmons - 4/7/1983 Elektra - la David Bellamy merv griffin theatre Andy Pierce Epic records 4/8 Carl Wilson rogers & cowan 4/12, Artist: Elektra Length: 01:30:39 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.27.mp3, 1.8.1.11.27.wav (Box 11, Cassette 27)
      - [Elektra] Lena Lovich 4/13/83 epic la Simple minds 4/15 a&m la Kiddo 4/15/83 a&m la Whispers 4/15 elektra la, Artist: Elektra Length: 01:40:29 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [Elektra] Elektra Demo, Artist: Elektra Length: 01:07:21 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.27.mp3, 1.8.1.12.27.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 27)
      - [Eurythmics] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: Eurythmics Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [FAA] FAA Excerpts Detroit Metro Tower Crash of NW 255, Artist: FAA Length: 01:26:54 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.28.mp3, 1.8.1.12.28.wav (Box 12, Cassette 28)
      - [Four Seasons] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Four Seasons Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Geldorf, Bob] TOM SCOTT- PAUL COLLINS/BOB GELDOFF- SHEEN MEMORIAL 5 TOM SCOTT/berkshire pl hotel #1521 12/7/79 * MEMORIAL FOR FULTON SHEET/st. pat's 12/10 cooke + McGarrick PAUL COLLINS/(the beat) WCBS 12/12 BOB GELDORF (boomtown rats) berkshire pl hotel #908 12/14/79 5, 1:38:12; Artist: Paul Collins Length: 01:38:12 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.15.mp3, 1.8.1.12.15.wav (Box 12, Cassette 15)
      - [Glass, Philip] Philip Glass, June Pointer 5/83 NYC. Zappa 6/15/83 CBS-D, Artist: Philip Glass Length: 00:49:09 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.29.mp3, 1.8.1.12.29.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 29)
      - [Goldenberg, Mark] Peter Bernstein/Mark Goldenberg Cretones 3/2/81 EA/KA Mark Case- Plimsouls ditto Mark Saffan 3/2/81 EA/LA, 0:01:05; Artist: Mark Goldenberg Length: 00:01:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.28.mp3, 1.8.1.11.28.wav (Box 11, Cassette 28)
      - [Goldmark, Andy] Wonder Gap Interview Andy GoldMark's 11/3/78 124 Univ Place NYC Solomon Skyy Roberts \ Trip to Calif 6/79 + VT, Artist: Andy Goldmark Length: 01:24:47 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.30.mp3, 1.8.1.12.30.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 30)
      - [Goodman, Steve] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Steve Goodman Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Hagan, Nina] Nina Hagen, Wire Train/In A Chamber, Artist: Nina Hagen Length: 01:21:2 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.31.mp3, 1.8.1.12.31.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 31)
      - [Hagan, Nina] Shut it tight Nina Hagen: NY, NY. Nina Hagen: Zarah Proof thru the night: The murder weapon, fatally beautiful, after all these years, baby fall down, the 60s, stunned, hula hoop, when the night falls, hefner + Disney Heartbeat city: Hello again, looking for live, magic, drive, stranger, U might think, its not the night, why cant I have you?, I refuse, heart beat city, Artist: Nina Hagan Length: 01:35:46 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.32.mp3, 1.8.1.12.32.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 32)
      - [Hall and Oates] Daryl Hall/John Oates Electric Lady 6/26/81 One and Two, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:01:03 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.33.mp3, 1.8.1.12.33.wav (Box 12, Cassette 33)
      - [Hall and Oates] Daryl Hall/John Oates Electric Lady 6/26/81 Three and FourBalde silva wcbs 9/18/79* MUSE harvey wasserman, james Taylor, John Hall, Graham Nash, Bonnie Raitt * Stsler Hilton 9/19/79\ DARYL HALL/JOHN OATES 45 sheridan sq, nyc 9/25/79 GENYA RaVAN cbs 10/17/79, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:01:00 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.34.mp3, 1.8.1.12.34.wav (Box 12, Cassette 34)
      - [Hall and Oates] Between the Lines: Hall & Oates #1-10, #11-20, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:02:00 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.33.mp3, 1.8.1.11.33.wav (Box 11, Cassette 33)
      - [Hall and Oates] Between the Lines: Hall & Oates segments 1-10 CBS Radio Peter Bekker \Between the Lines: Hall & Oates segments 11-20 peter bekker, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:22:29 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.34.mp3, 1.8.1.11.34.wav (Box 11, Cassette 34)
      - [Hall and Oates] Daryl Hall/John Oates-Genya Ravan Balde Silva - Muse News conference\ 1) balde silva wcbs 9/18/79 * MUSE harvey wasserman, james taylor, john hall, graham nash, bonnie raitt * stsler hilton 9/19/79\2) Daryll Hall /John Oates 45 Sheridan sq, nyc 9/25/79 Genya Ravan cbs 10/17/79, Artist: Hall and Oates Length: 01:02:04 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.35.mp3, 1.8.1.11.35.wav (Box 11, Cassette 35)